<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="whats_new_dialog_text">
<b>Do you like RMaps?\n
Buy RMaps.Donation on Google Play Store</b>\n
\n
Do you want to help me translate the app interface? Write me to email robertk506@gmail.com\n
\n
v.0.9.1\n
+ BING maps (Roag, Aerial , Hydrid)\n
- Offline maps bug fix
\n
v.0.9.0\n
+ Tile downloader\n
+ Sort POI, tracks\n
\n
v.0.8.12\n
+ New overlay feature (add overlay layer above map by one touch, create your own map+overlay pairs, flexibility overlay button on the map)\n
+ New ability to add your own map source\n
\n
v.0.8.11\n
+ New maps Cloudmade (OSM data) with comfort label size\n
+ Google scale factor. You can enlarge size of the labels on the map. See the preference of the map\n
+ Language preference. You can set UI language independent of system\n
+ Imperial units in statistic view\n
+ Track color, width, shadow\n
+ Multiple tracks on the map\n
\n
v.0.8.10.2\n
+ Support geo intents. You can tap address in calendar app and show it in RMaps\n
- Bugfix support MNM files and c:geo app\n
\n
v.0.8.10\n
+ UI updates\n
+ Maps URL updates\n
\n
v.0.8.9\n
+ Crosshair on centre of the map\n
+ Added new map maps.refuges.info\n
\n
v.0.8.8\n
+ Update maps URL\n
- UI improvement for high res screens\n
\n
v.0.8.7\n
+ New preference Directory\n
+ Now RMaps stores tiles of online maps on sdcard in sqlite format\n
\n
v.0.8.6\n
+ New maps: VFR (avcharts.com), MyTopo, OSM MTB Mapa Česká republika\n
+ Error report (please, send me message about force close)\n
- Bug fix: Mutlitouch, Scale bar, more\n
\n
v.0.8.5\n
+ Scale bar, Units property\n
\n
v.0.8.4\n
-  Mutlitouch zooming\n
+ Zoom buttons settings: top, bottom, hide\n
\n
v.0.8.3.2\n
+ Ready to install to SD card\n
+ Update maps URL\n
- Bug fix: Force close on Stop trackwriter on Froyo\n
- Bug fix: Wrong date time on tracks. New tracks will be OK\n
\n
v.0.8.3\n
+ Export track to GPX, KML file\n
\n
v.0.8.2\n
+ Drawing of a current written track\n
\n
v.0.8.1\n
+ Track writer\n
+ Integration with Radar programs\n
+ New maps for USA aviators: VFR Chart, IFR Low, IFR High\n
\n
v.0.8.0\n
+ Import tracks from KML, GPX files\n
\n
v.0.7.7.1\n
- Bug fix: Import some poi files\n
+ Delete all poi confirm dialog\n
\n
v.0.7.7\n
+ Import POI from KML, GPX files\n
+ Optimisation of drawing of POI\n
+ Update Yandex.Map URL, Google.Map URL\n
\n
v.0.7.6\n
+ Add localisation of Google Maps. See Preference\n
+ Added new online maps (Topographic map of Norway, Sea map of Norway)\n
+ Add screen orientation preference\n
+ Update Yandex.Map URL, Google.Map URL\n
\n
v.0.7.5\n
+ POI category\n
+ The back button close the search result window\n
- Bug fix: OS Map\n
\n
v.0.7.4\n
+ Added new online maps (Docelu.pl Poland, Freemap.sk Slovakia, Slovakia Hiking, Slovakia Hiking HillShade)\n
Do you want to add new online map? Write to me.\n
\n
v.0.7.3\n
- Bug fix: 100 value zoom in sqlitedb format maps\n
+ Added new online maps (Microsoft Maps, Maps China, Virtual Earth, Hybrid, OSM Hiking Germany, OSM Public Transport, Outdooractive.com, Cykloatlas CZ, UMP-pcPL Poland)\n
\n
v.0.7.0\n
+ Minimum POI functionality\n
+ Integration with GPS Status by Rudolf Hornig\n
+ Move index data of offline maps to sdcard\n
+ Added buttons for clearing internal cache and index database to preference\n
+ Update Yandex.Map URL, Google.Map URL\n
- Bug fix: Wrong compass orientation on landscape mode\n
\n
	</string>
</resources>